{
  "level": 2,
  "unit": 2,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a person or animal that is fully grown.",
          "answer": "adult"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If something is _____________, it is living.",
          "answer": "alive"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If something is _____________, there is something all over it.",
          "answer": "covered"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is thick animal hair. Something that is giant is very large.",
          "answer": "fur"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is _____________ is very large.",
          "answer": "giant"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When animals _____________ each other, they clean each other.",
          "answer": "groom"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is any warm-blooded animal that feeds milk to its babies.",
          "answer": "mammal"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are the children or young of people or animals.",
          "answer": "offspring"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________ something, you think it is true.",
          "answer": "believe"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When food is _____________, it tastes very good.",
          "answer": "delicious"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________, you eat a large or fancy meal.",
          "answer": "feast"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you are _____________ of something, you like it a lot.",
          "answer": "fond"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are things you can learn from.",
          "answer": "lessons"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If something is _____________, it is wonderful or outstanding.",
          "answer": "remarkable"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you _____________ something, you grab it quickly.",
          "answer": "snatch"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you tell _____________, you tell made-up tales.",
          "answer": "stories"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "When you _____________ , you act in a way that is good or correct.",
          "answer": "behave"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are the soft things that cover a birdâ€™s body.",
          "answer": "feathers"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If something is _____________ , it is moving up and down.",
          "answer": "flapping"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you _____________ your feelings, you tell or show how you feel about something.",
          "answer": "express"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a form of writing that expresses imagination or feelings.",
          "answer": "poem"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When two words _____________ , they have the same ending sounds.",
          "answer": "rhyme"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the repeating accents, or beats, in a poem.",
          "answer": "rhythm"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the use of rich, colorful, exact words.",
          "answer": "word choice"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
